prosource.net 2019-01-07

# Privacy Policy – Prosource

ProSource respects the privacy of every visitor to our website. Any information that has been submitted will not be made available to any other source other than for shipping purposes. Our site uses IP information solely for the identification of our customers and account information. We will never sell or allow this information to be used by other companies for soliciting purposes. This site contains links to other sites. ProSource is not responsible for the privacy practices, representations, or the content of such third party websites.

We retain customer's contact information (name, email address, shipping address, phone numbers). This contact information is used to send and track orders placed by our customers. To ensure your financial protection, we do not retain credit card numbers. Credit card numbers must be submitted each time an order is placed.

Our forum is public domain. All registered user names are retained with email addresses and IP addresses for identification purposes only. This registration information is not available to the public, unless the user chooses it to be. Threads and replies that are posted on our forum by registered users becomes available to the public. Please refrain from posting any personal information not intended for public view.

ProSource periodically sends emails to registered users with current news and sales information. We also provide the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us with the using the "unsubscribe" option provided in our emails.

If you are a California resident, and a ProSource customer, you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the address below.

Should you have any further questions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please write to us at: Customer Service; ProSource, 2231 Landmark Place, Manasquan, NJ 08736; or Contact our Customer Service Department at: [customerservice@prosource.net](mailto:customerservice@prosource.net)

Any questions about our privacy statement can be sent to: [webmaster@prosource.net](mailto:webmaster@prosource.net)
